<resources>
    <string name="app_name_icon">FDA MyStudies Demo</string>
    <string name="app_name">FDA MyStudies Demo</string>
    <string name="fda_listens">FDA MyStudies Demo</string>
    <string name="website">https://www.fda.gov/drugs/science-and-research-drugs/fdas-mystudies-application-app</string>
    <string name="websitetxt">www.fda.gov</string>
    <string name="gateway_des">The FDA is pleased to offer the FDA MyStudies Demonstration app as a tool to evaluate the FDA MyStudies system for your own clinical research purposes.</string>
    <string name="gateway_des1">Using this app with the other elements of the FDA MyStudies Demonstration System, researchers, regulators and other potential users can better understand the features of the FDA MyStudies system and decide if it is suitable for their research goals.</string>
    <string name="delete_account_content">You have chosen to delete your FDA MyStudies Demo Account. This will result in automatic withdrawal from all studies.\n\nBelow is a list of studies that you are a part of and information on how your response data will be handled with each after you withdraw. Please review and confirm.</string>
    <string name="delete_message">Are you sure you wish to permanently delete your FDA Health Studies Gateway app Demo account?  You will need to register again if you wish to join a study.</string>
    <string name="my_studies">MyStudies</string>
    <string name="studie_your_enrolled">It\'s been a while since you visited the FDA MyStudies Demo app. Please consider continuing your participation in any studies in which you\'re enrolled.</string>
    <string name="prject_name">FDA</string>


    <string name="termsurl">https://wcp.demo.mystudiesapp.org/fdahpStudyDesigner/TermsAndConditions.do</string>
    <string name="privacyurl">https://wcp.demo.mystudiesapp.org/fdahpStudyDesigner/TermsAndConditions.do</string>

    <string name="view_consent">View Consent</string>
    <string name="visit_website">Visit Website</string>
    <string name="join_study">Join Study</string>
    <string name="per_completion">There are no more activities for this study in the COVID MyStudies app. Thank you for your participation.</string>

    <!--must change strings-->
    <string name="FileProvider_authorities">com.myfileprovider.demo</string>
</resources>
