<resources>
    <string name="app_name_icon">CARRA Registry</string><!--live-->
    <!--<string name="app_name_icon">CARRA Registry Test</string>--><!--test-->
    <string name="app_name">CARRA Registry</string>
    <string name="fda_listens">CARRA Registry</string>
    <string name="website">https://carragroup.org/</string>
    <string name="websitetxt">www.carragroup.org</string>
    <string name="gateway_des">CARRA is pleased to offer the LIMIT-JIA Trial app as a tool to gather data about medication use and other health issues facing the people we serve.</string>
    <string name="gateway_des1">Available for iOS and Android devices, this app will house surveys conducted by CARRA and other institutions for LIMIT-JIA.  This will allow researchers to engage more directly with people to gather data through surveys.</string>
    <string name="delete_account_content">You have chosen to delete your CARRA Registry Account. This will result in automatic withdrawal from all studies.\n\nBelow is a list of studies that you are a part of and information on how your response data will be handled with each after you withdraw. Please review and confirm.</string>
    <string name="delete_message">Are you sure you wish to permanently delete your CARRA Registry Gateway app account?  You will need to register again if you wish to join a study.</string>
    <string name="studie_your_enrolled">It\'s been a while since you visited the CARRA Registry app. Please consider continuing your participation in any studies in which you\'re enrolled.</string>
    <string name="prject_name">CARRA Registry</string>
    <string name="my_studies">CARRA Registry</string>


    <!--Added additionally for LimitJia-->
    <string name="join_study">Get Started&#33;</string>
    <string name="per_completion">There are no more activities for this study in the COVID MyStudies app. Thank you for your participation.</string>
    <string name="validated">You\'re In</string>
    <string name="you_are_eligible">You\'re In</string>
    <string name="gateway_welcome1">Using Mobile Devices to Power Research</string>
    <string name="termsurl">https://carragroup.org/privacy-policy</string>
    <string name="privacyurl">https://carragroup.org/privacy-policy</string>

    <string name="view_consent">View Consent</string>
    <string name="visit_website">Visit Website</string>

    <!--must change strings-->
    <string name="FileProvider_authorities">com.myfileprovider.limitjia</string>
</resources>
